HERE Western Region Local Files 6199/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Western Region Local Files
1971-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/002
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records.
5840645
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 25, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199 AV: HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 G: HERE Graphics 6199 MB: HERE Memorabilia 6199 mf: HERE Records on Microfilm 6199 PUBS: HERE Publications 6199/001: HERE Legislative Department Files 6199/003: HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files 6199/003 mf: HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/004: HERE Locals files 6199/004 mf: HERE Locals Files on Microfilm 6199/005: HERE Communications Department Files 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/006: HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006 mf: HERE General Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf: HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/008 mf: HERE General President's Files on Microfilm 6199/009 mf: HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf: HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/011 mf: HERE Official Journals on Microfilm 6199/012 mf: HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/013: HERE Historical Files 6199/013 P: HERE Historical Photographs 6199/014: HERE Conventions Files 6199/015: HERE Editor Files
Hotel & Restaurant Employees International Union; Walt Disney Company; Universal City Studios; Paramount Pictures Corporation
5840645
- Brown Reception, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Governor Brown, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Hy Klayman, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Joint Board- Bylaws and Delegates, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Joint Board- Master File, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Joint Council- Southern California, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles Joint Board. Norm's Strike, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Joint Board, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- William Kircher, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Local 2. San Francisco, CA. Strike (Folder 1), 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Local 2. San Francisco, CA. Strike (Folder 2), 1971-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Local 2. San Francisco, CA. Strike (Folder 3), 1971-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Local 2. San Francisco, CA. Strike (Folder 4- Newspaper), 1971-1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Local 11. Los Angeles, CA. Covey and Covey. Building Sale and Lease, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Local 11. Los Angeles, CA., 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Local 11. Los Angeles, CA. (Folder 1) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Local 11. Los Angeles, CA. (Folder 2), 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Local 226. Las Vegas, NV., 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Local 226. Las Vegas, NV. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Scope and Contents
  Additional info
- Local 226. Las Vegas, NV. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Newsletter
- Local 11. Los Angeles, CA. Joint Board, 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Corey and Corey Local 11 Building Sale and Lease (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Local 11. Los Angeles, CA. Trusteeship, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Local 28. Oakland, CA. Trusteeship (folder 1 of 2), 1976-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Local 28. Oakland, CA. Trusteeship (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Local 86. Reno, NV., 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Local 483. Monterey, CA., 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Local 483. Monterey, CA. Negotiations, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 631. Phoenix, AZ. (Folder 1), 1974-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Local 631. Phoenix, AZ. (Folder 2), 1974-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Local 531. Pasadena, CA. (Folder 1), 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Local 531. Pasadena, CA. (Folder 2), 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Burbank Studios, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Metro Goldwyn Mayer Film Company, 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Motion Picture Studio Negotiations, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Paramount Pictures Corporation (Folder 1), 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Paramount Pictures Corporation (Folder 2), 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Paramount Pictures Corporation (Folder 3), 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Studio Catering Company, Inc., 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Universal City Studios, Inc. (Folder 1), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Universal City Studios, Inc. (Folder 2), 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Universal City Studios, Inc. (Folder 3), 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Universal and Lorimar Studio Contracts, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Universal Severance, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Wally Branch Enterprises, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Wally Branch / Burbank Studios, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Walt Disney Co. (Folder 1), 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Walt Disney Co. (Folder 2), 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Fox Studios Negotiations, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)